Railway Labor Executives' Association Additional Records 5552
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Government. Transportation Association of America, 1972 (Box 25, Folder 17)
- Government. DOT Studies, 1972 (Box 25, Folder 18)
- Government. National Transportation Safety Board, 1972 (Box 25, Folder 19)
  Includes NTSB accident reports
- Government. DOT, Report to Congress, Highway-Railroad Safety, 1972 (Box 25, Folder 20)
- Government. Federal Railroad Administration, 1972 (Box 25, Folder 21)
- Government. Federal Railroad Administration, Staff Appointments, 1972 (Box 25, Folder 22)
- Government. Office of High Speed Ground Transportation, 1972 (Box 25, Folder 23)
- Government. Bureau of Railroad Safety, 1972 (Box 25, Folder 24)
- Government. Railroad Task Force, 1972 (Box 25, Folder 25)
- Government. Safety - Rules, Regulations, Petitions (FRA-DOT), 1972 (Box 25, Folder 26)
- Government. Highway Grade Crossing Matters, 1972 (Box 25, Folder 27)
- Government. Power Brakes, 1972 (Box 25, Folder 28)
- Government. Locomotive Inspection, 1972 (Box 25, Folder 29)
- Government. Signal Rules, Standards and Instructions Cases, 1972 (Box 25, Folder 30)
- Government. Approval of Changes in Signal Installations (BS-AP/Cases), 1972 (Box 25, Folder 31)
- Government. Hours of Service, 1972 (Box 25, Folder 32)
- Government. Track Maintenance and Inspection Standards, 1972 (Box 25, Folder 33)
  Filings regarding different carriers before OSHA
- Government. Department of Labor Statistics Bulletin, 1972 (Box 25, Folder 34)
- Government. Accident Reports and Governing Regulations, 1972 (Box 25, Folder 35)
- Government. Labor Department - General, 1972 (Box 25, Folder 36)
- Government. Bureau of Labor Statistics, 1972 (Box 25, Folder 37)
- Government. Bureau of Labor-Managers Reports, 1972 (Box 25, Folder 38)
- Government. Occupational Safety and Health Administration (OSHA), 1972 (Box 25, Folder 39)
- Government. Interstate Commerce Commission - General, 1972 (Box 25, Folder 40)
- Government. ICC Membership and Staff Appointments, 1972 (Box 25, Folder 41)
- Government. ICC Rules of Practice and Administrative Procedure, 1972 (Box 25, Folder 42)
- Government. ICC Statistics, 1972 (Box 25, Folder 43)
- Government. Statistics 240 Motive Power and Car Equip., 1972 (Box 25, Folder 44)
- Government. Statistics 300-350 Steam Railways - Class I Wages, Monthly, 1972 (Box 25, Folder 45)
- Government. Car Service Orders, 1972 (Box 25, Folder 46)
- Government. Ex Parte 278, Equal Opportunity in Surface Transportation, 1972 (Box 25, Folder 47)
  Filings by various parties in the proceedings.
- Government. Bureau of Transport Economics and Statistics - General, 1972 (Box 26, Folder 1)
- Government. ICC Ex Parte No. 274 (Sub. No. 1) Special Procedures for Proposed Railroad Abandonments, 1972 (Box 26, Folder 2)
- Government. National Mediation Board - General, 1972 (Box 26, Folder 3)
  Mediation between UTU and U.S. Carriers
- Government. National Mediation Board, Emergency Board Reports, 1972 (Box 26, Folder 4a)
  Includes reports of Emergency Boards 180 and 182.
- Government. National Mediation Board, Public Law Board Decisions on Procedural Questions, 1972 (Box 26, Folder 4b)
- Government. National Mediation Board Membership and Staff Appointments, 1972 (Box 26, Folder 5)
- Government. National Mediation Board, Rules of Procedures and Administration 107:2, 1972 (Box 26, Folder 6)
- Government. National Mediation Board, Amendments re Individuals as Bargaining Agents [folder 1 of 4], 1972 (Box 26, Folder 7a)
- Government. National Mediation Board, Appropriations, 1972 (Box 26, Folder 7b)
  No records contained in folder when collection accessioned. No records contained in folder when collection accessioned. No records contained in folder when collection accessioned. No records contained in folder when collection accessioned.
- Government. National Mediation Board, Lists of carriers and Designated Officers to Handle Disputes, 1972 (Box 26, Folder 7c)
- Government. National Mediation Board, Monthly Reports on Status of Cases, 1972 (Box 26, Folder 7d)
- Government. National Mediation Board, Decisions and Certifications, 1972 (Box 26, Folder 8)
- Government. National Railroad Adjustment Board - General, 1972 (Box 26, Folder 9)
- Government. National Railroad Adjustment Board, Third Division, 1972 (Box 26, Folder 10)
- Government. National Railroad Adjustment Board, Fourth Division, 1972 (Box 26, Folder 11)
- Government. National Railroad Adjustment Board, Orgs. Qualified to Participate in Selection of Members, 1972 (Box 26, Folder 12)
- Government. National Railroad Adjustment Board, Membership, 1972 (Box 26, Folder 13)
- Government. National Railroad Adjustment Board, Applications of Awards, 1972 (Box 26, Folder 14)
- Government. Railroad Retirement Board - General, 1972 (Box 26, Folder 15)
  Includes quarterly reports on finances and broadsides advocating for pension reform.
- Government. Railroad Retirement Board - General, 1972 (Box 26, Folder 16)
- Government. Railroad Retirement Board, Reports for RLEA Meeting from Railroad Board, 1972 (Box 26, Folder 17)
- Government. Railroad Retirement Board, Membership and Staff Appointments, 1972 (Box 26, Folder 18)
- Government. Railroad Retirement Board, Field Offices, 1972 (Box 26, Folder 19)
- Government. Railroad Retirement Board, Coverage of Railroads and Unions as Employers, 1972 (Box 26, Folder 20)
- Government. Railroad Retirement Board, Status of Funds - Actuarial Reports, 1972 (Box 26, Folder 21)
- Government. Railroad Retirement Board, Railroad Retirement Benefit and Unemployment Insurance Systems, 1972 (Box 26, Folder 22)
  Pamphlet on 1972 Amendments to Railroad Retirement Act
- Government. Railroad Retirement Board, National Reporting Officers' Memoranda, 1972 (Box 26, Folder 23a)
- Government. Railroad Retirement Board, National Reporting Officers' Memoranda, 1972 (Box 26, Folder 23b)
- Government. Administration of Medicare - Financial Intermediary, 1972 (Box 26, Folder 24)
- Government. Commission on Railroad Retirement [folder 1 of 2], 1972 (Box 27, Folder 1a)
  Includes report to presidents, drafts, statistical analysis, correspondence, and financial reports.
- Government. Commission on Railroad Retirement [folder 2 of 2], 1972 (Box 27, Folder 1b)
- Government. President's Committee on the Physically Handicapped 111:0, 1972 (Box 27, Folder 2)
- Government. Civil Aeronautics Board, 1972 (Box 27, Folder 3)
- Government. National Railroad Passenger Corp. (AMTRAK) [folder 1 of 2], 1972 (Box 27, Folder 4a)
  Includes information on passes, passenger routes and stations, Agreements, and amendments to bill creating Amtrak.
- Government. National Railroad Passenger Corp. (Amtrak) [folder 2 of 2], 1972 (Box 27, Folder 4b)
- Government. President's Committee on Equal Employment Opportunity, 1972 (Box 27, Folder 5)
- Government. Fast Freight Systems Transportation Corporation (Act), 1972 (Box 27, Folder 6)
- Government. Civil Rights (Agenda Item 2:19) formerly 3.66), 1972 (Box 27, Folder 7)
- Government. Economic Stabilization Pay Board, 1971 (Box 27, Folder 8)
- Government. White House Conference on the Industrial World Ahead, 1972 (Box 27, Folder 9)
- Judicial. Court Cases General, 1972 (Box 27, Folder 10)
- Judicial. Penn Central Bankruptcy, 1972 (Box 27, Folder 11)
- Judicial. Boston and Maine Reorganization (CA #70-250), 1972 (Box 27, Folder 12)
- Judicial. Lehigh Valley Reorganization, 1972 (Box 27, Folder 13)
- Judicial. Reading Reorganization U.S.D.C. Ed Pa. No. 71-828, 1972 (Box 27, Folder 14)
- Judicial. Central Railroad Co. of New Jersey Reorganization, 1972 (Box 27, Folder 15)
- Judicial. Jacksonville Terminal (Civil Rights), 1972 (Box 27, Folder 16)
- Judicial. Erie-Lackawanna Railway Reorganization, 1972 (Box 27, Folder 17)
- RLEA. RLEA General, 1972 (Box 27, Folder 18)
- RLEA. RLEA Emergency Relief Fund, 1972 (Box 27, Folder 19)
- RLEA. Constitution and By-Laws, 1972 (Box 27, Folder 20)
- RLEA. Officers and Members, 1972 (Box 27, Folder 21)
- RLEA. American Railway Supervisors Association, 1972 (Box 27, Folder 22)
- RLEA. American Train Dispatchers Association, Attempted Raid by Rump Organizations, 1971-1972 (Box 27, Folder 23)
- RLEA. American Train Dispatchers Association, 1972 (Box 27, Folder 24)
- RLEA. Brotherhood of Railroad Signalmen, 1973 (Box 27, Folder 25)
- RLEA. Brotherhood of Sleeping Car Porters, 1972 (Box 27, Folder 26)
- RLEA. International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers, 1972 (Box 27, Folder 27)
- RLEA. International Brotherhood of Boilermakers and Blacksmiths, 1972 (Box 27, Folder 28)
- RLEA. Railway Employees' Dept. AFL-CIO, 1972 (Box 27, Folder 29)
- RLEA. Sheet Metal Workers International Association, 1972 (Box 27, Folder 30)
- RLEA. Brotherhood of Locomotive Engineers, 1972 (Box 27, Folder 31)
- RLEA. RLEA Meetings - General, 1972 (Box 27, Folder 32)
- RLEA. Miami Meeting of RLEA, 1973 (Box 27, Folder 33)
  Includes planning documents, hotel brochures and minutes of meetings
- RLEA. Agendas, 1972 (Box 27, Folder 34)
  for monthly meetings.
- RLEA. Reports of Counsel, 1972 (Box 27, Folder 35)
- RLEA. Assessments, 1972 (Box 27, Folder 36)
- RLEA. Wages and Rules - General, 1972 (Box 27, Folder 37)
- RLEA. Radio-Telephone Equipment Communications, 1972 (Box 27, Folder 38)
- RLEA. Florida East Coast Railway, 1972 (Box 27, Folder 39)
- RLEA. Employment and Medical Examination Policy and Procedures, 1972 (Box 27, Folder 40)
- RLEA. 1970 Wage-Rules Movement, 1972 (Box 27, Folder 41)
- RLEA. Health and Welfare, 1972 (Box 27, Folder 42)
- RLEA. Traveler's Insurance Company [folder 1 of 2], 1972 (Box 27, Folder 43a)
  Group policies
- RLEA. Travelers' Insurance Company [folder 2 of 2], 1972 (Box 27, Folder 43b)
- RLEA. Miami Meeting of RLEA, 1972 (Box 28, Folder 1)
- RLEA. Railway Labor Building, 1972 (Box 28, Folder 2)
- RLEA. Committees - General, 1972 (Box 28, Folder 3)
- RLEA. Safety Committee, 1972 (Box 28, Folder 4)
- RLEA. Committee to Study Railroad Mergers, Consolidations, Etc., 1972 (Box 28, Folder 5)
- RLEA. Committee to Meet with AAR, Railroad Labor-Management Relations, 1972 (Box 28, Folder 6)
- RLEA. AAR-RLEA Committee On Equal Employment Opportunity, 1972 (Box 28, Folder 7)
- RLEA. Committee on Railroad Retirement, 1972 (Box 28, Folder 8)
- RLEA. Committee on Railway Labor Act, 1972 (Box 28, Folder 9)
- RLEA. Committee to Study RLEA Operating Costs, 1972 (Box 28, Folder 10)
- RLEA. Passes, 1972 (Box 28, Folder 11)
- RLEA. Financial Statements, 1972 (Box 28, Folder 12)
- RLEA. Workmen's Compensation Tax, 1972 (Box 28, Folder 13)
- RLEA. Postage Meter, 1972 (Box 28, Folder 14)
- RLEA. Addressograph-Multigraph Corporation, 1972 (Box 28, Folder 15)
- RLEA. Office Equipment - General, 1971 (Box 28, Folder 16)
- RLEA. Xerox Copying Machine, 1972 (Box 28, Folder 17)
- RLEA. Lawyers - General, 1972 (Box 28, Folder 18)
- RLEA. Lawyer's Bills [folder 1 of 3], 1972 (Box 28, Folder 19a)
  Itemized by legal matter
- RLEA. Lawyer's Bills [folder 2 of 3], 1972 (Box 28, Folder 19b)
- RLEA. Lawyer's Bills [folder 3 of 3], 1972 (Box 28, Folder 19c)
- RLEA. Strikes - General, 1972 (Box 28, Folder 20)
- RLEA. Florida East Coast Railway Strike, 1972 (Box 28, Folder 21)
  Includes signed agreement between carrier and railroad Shop Crafts.
- Railroads. Railroads - General, 1972 (Box 28, Folder 22)
- Railroads. Penn Central, 1972 (Box 28, Folder 23)
- Railroads. Illinois Central, 1972 (Box 28, Folder 24)
  Memoranda of Agreement and Employee Protection Agreements in re merger between Illinois Central and the Gulf, Mobile and Ohio Railroad.
- Railroads. Auto Train Corp., 1972 (Box 28, Folder 25)
- Railroads. Association of American Railroads [folder 1 of 2], 1972 (Box 28, Folder 26a)
- Railroads. Association of American Railroads [folder 2 of 2], 1972 (Box 28, Folder 26b)
- Railroads. Western Railroad Association (Formerly Assn. of Western Railways), 1972 (Box 28, Folder 27)
- Railroads. National Railway Labor Conference, 1972 (Box 28, Folder 28)
- Railroads. Hospital Associations - General, 1972 (Box 28, Folder 29)
- Railroads. Hospital Associations - Medicare, 1972 (Box 28, Folder 30)
- Other Organizations. AFL-CIO - General, 1972 (Box 28, Folder 31)
- Other Organizations. AFL-CIO, Civil Rights, 1972 (Box 28, Folder 32)
- Other Organizations. AFL-CIO, COPE, 1972 (Box 28, Folder 33)
- Other Organizations. AFL-CIO Legislation Action Bulletin, 1972 (Box 28, Folder 34)
- Other Organizations. AFL-CIO, Legislative Council, 1972 (Box 28, Folder 35)
- Other Organizations. AFL-CIO, Executive Council, 1972 (Box 28, Folder 36)
- Other Organizations. Miscellaneous Organizations - General, 1972 (Box 29, Folder 1)
- Other Organizations. National Safety Council, 1972 (Box 29, Folder 2)
- Other Organizations. Research Institute of American Recommendations, 1972 (Box 29, Folder 3)
- Other Organizations. Transportation Research Forum, 1972 (Box 29, Folder 4)
- Other Organizations. The Labor-Management Committee for Fair Foreign Competition, 1972 (Box 29, Folder 5)
- Other Organizations. Charities - General, 1972 (Box 29, Folder 6)
- Other Organizations. Labor Newspaper, 1972 (Box 29, Folder 7)
- Other Organizations. Special Election Year Editions of Labor, 1972 (Box 29, Folder 8)
- Other Organizations. City of Hope, 1972 (Box 29, Folder 9)
- Other Organizations. National Transportation Week, 1972 (Box 29, Folder 10)
- Other Organizations. NARP, 1972 (Box 29, Folder 11)
- International Affairs. International Affairs, General, 1972 (Box 29, Folder 12)
- Commuter Problems. Commuter Service Improvements - HUD - Mass. Transit Grants, 1972 (Box 29, Folder 13)
  Chicago, Delaware, Connecticut, NJT,
- Commuter Problems. Sect. 13(c) Agreement, Massachusetts Bay Transit Authority, 1972 (Box 29, Folder 14)
- Commuter Problems. Sect. 13(c) Agreement, Chicago Transit Authority - Loop and West Suburban, 1972 (Box 29, Folder 15)
- Commuter Problems. Washington DC Metro Area Transit Authority, 1972 (Box 29, Folder 16)
- International Affairs. Office of International Labor Affairs - ILAB, 1972 (Box 29, Folder 17)
- International Affairs. Team Managers - O.I.L.A., 1972 (Box 29, Folder 18)
- International Affairs. International Transport Workers' Federation, 1972 (Box 29, Folder 19)
- Commuter Problems. Commuter Problems - General, 1972 (Box 29, Folder 20)
- Commuter Problems. Commuter Problems Philadelphia Service Improvement Corp., 1972 (Box 29, Folder 21)
- Commuter Problems. New Haven Problems Including New York Area (Long Island) (Staten Island), 1972 (Box 29, Folder 22)
- Commuter Problems. New England Railroad Study, 1972 (Box 29, Folder 23)
- Commuter Problems. Bay Area Rapid Transit (BART), 1972 (Box 29, Folder 24)
- Commuter Problems. Port Authority Trans Hudson (PATH), 1972 (Box 29, Folder 25)
- Commuter Problems. Adequacies - General, 1972 (Box 29, Folder 26)